<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Andromeda Law</title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Andromeda Law</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/benjamin_waterman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/benjamin_waterman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-benjamin-waterman&#34;&gt;About Benjamin Waterman&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dedicated to Providing Clear and Effective Legal Representation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Benjamin Miller Waterman has been practicing law in Ontario since 2018, bringing over six years of experience across a range of legal matters. Representing clients from individuals to large corporations. His practice focuses on civil litigation and employment law, providing strategic and practical advice to help clients navigate complex legal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-background&#34;&gt;Professional Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Benjamin graduated from Western Law at the University of Western Ontario in 2017 and was called to the Bar of Ontario in 2018. Before establishing Andromeda Law, he practiced at a full-service law firm, handling a diverse caseload. His experience includes:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booking</title>
      <link>/about/booking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/booking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;booking-an-appointment&#34;&gt;Booking an Appointment&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scheduling a consultation with &lt;strong&gt;Andromeda Law&lt;/strong&gt; is simple and convenient. Our online booking system allows you to choose a time that fits your schedule, ensuring a seamless and stress-free experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-book&#34;&gt;How to Book&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose Your Service&lt;/strong&gt;: Select the type of legal consultation you need from our &lt;a href=&#34;/practice_areas/&#34;&gt;services page&lt;/a&gt;. This helps us prepare for your specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pick a Date and Time&lt;/strong&gt;: Use our &lt;a href=&#34;https://lawtap.com/ca/law-firms/andromeda-law&#34;&gt;online booking tool&lt;/a&gt; to view available time slots and choose one that works for you. We offer extended hours to accommodate various schedules.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancellation Policy</title>
      <link>/about/cancellation_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/cancellation_policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;cancellation-policy&#34;&gt;Cancellation Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Andromeda Law&lt;/strong&gt;, we understand that schedules can change unexpectedly. Our cancellation and rescheduling policies are designed to be fair and considerate for both our clients and our practice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note:&lt;/strong&gt; This cancellation policy applies to non-retainer clients scheduling prepaid consultations. Clients who have an ongoing retainer agreement with us are not subject to cancellation fees; however, cancellations or rescheduling may result in additional billable time due to preparation and administrative efforts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rates</title>
      <link>/about/rates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/rates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;clear-and-transparent-pricing&#34;&gt;Clear and Transparent Pricing&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Andromeda Law&lt;/strong&gt;, we believe in making legal costs straightforward and transparent. We offer competitive hourly rates and flat fees for specific services to help you understand the expenses involved from the outset. Please note that all fees are subject to Harmonized Sales Tax (HST) as required by Ontario law.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;hourly-rate&#34;&gt;Hourly Rate&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our general hourly rate is &lt;strong&gt;$300 per hour&lt;/strong&gt;. This rate applies to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Litigation&lt;/strong&gt;: Representation in civil litigation matters, including complex cases in the Superior Court of Justice and the Ontario Court of Appeal.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Legal Advice&lt;/strong&gt;: Consultations and advice on various legal matters not covered by our flat-fee services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewing/Updating Existing Employment Contracts&lt;/strong&gt;: For employers looking to review or update their current employment contracts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;free-15-minute-consultation&#34;&gt;Free 15-Minute Consultation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For litigation matters billed at our general hourly rate (such as Superior Court cases, defending Small Claims, or more complex Small Claims cases), we offer a &lt;strong&gt;free 15-minute initial consultation&lt;/strong&gt;. This allows us to assess your situation and determine how we can assist you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
